[theme music playing]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks, fires]
[whoosh, slashing sounds]
[machine gun fire]
[machine gun fire continues]
[single gunshot]
[rapid gunfire]
[echoing blast]
[blade whooshing]
[tense music builds]
[Camia] Your father always wanted
to walk you down the aisle
at your wedding.
[Diego] I can't wait.
I'm so excited to start
my new life with my wife.
Mayor, we've tracked them down.
They're at the St. Monica
chapel in Rosario.
Lily, no matter how many times I fall,
no matter how many times I get hurt,
I'll never stop loving you.
I promise to love you
until my last breath.
[Lily] The love we share
is among the few good things
going on in my life right now.
I'm very happy right now, Diego.
[Arnaldo] I found Lily and Diego.
And guess what?
They just got married. I wasn't invited.
Come home. Leave them there.
[Arnaldo] But I want to thank you
for always taking care of me.
I love you.
[Julio] And I love you too, my son.
You always remember that.
[Diego] I think I'm the happiest
and luckiest guy on earth,
Mrs. Lily Cruz-Torillo.
[Dante] Lily.
Dad.
Lily, your lives are in danger. Wake up.
[ominous music playing]
[Arnaldo] Be quiet and don't move.
Shh. Sorry. Sorry for ruining
your honeymoon. Quiet.
I'm here to kill your husband.
I'll end his life tonight.
[groans]
Dieg--
[grunts] Diego!
-Shut up!
-Dieg--
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[dramatic music playing]
Diego.
-[grunts]
-[groans]
Come here.
[screams]
No!
[dark music playing]
[Arnaldo] Lily!
Come back here!
I said come back!
Lily!
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
You bastard!
-[Arnaldo grunts]
-[Lily groans]
No!
[screams] Somebody, help her!
Don't you get it? It's just us now.
You're all mine. All mine!
I'll… I'll never be yours!
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[Lily cries]
Don't! Arnaldo!
[screaming]
[Lily grunts]
[ominous music playing]
-[gunshots]
-Arnaldo!
[gunshots]
Arnaldo!
Get your hands off my wife!
I'll never let you be happy!
[Arnaldo screaming]
[Diego groans]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Arnaldo] I don't care if you have a gun!
I don't give a damn!
[Diego grunting]
[Arnaldo] Go ahead! Come on!
-Diego!
-Come on!
-Arnaldo, stop this!
-No!
[groaning]
Diego!
[Diego groaning]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Diego groans]
Don't!
Arnaldo, don't!
[Diego] No! Arnaldo!
[Diego] Lily!
[Diego] Arnaldo! Arnaldo!
[Lily] Don't do this!
Don't kill your brother!
[Diego groaning]
Arnaldo! Arnaldo, please!
Please, stop this!
We're begging you, please stop! Just stop!
I'll never let you be happy!
Never.
Go ahead. Just do it. Go ahead, Arnaldo!
Pull it! Pull the trigger!
Do it, Arnaldo! Kill us!
If you're going to kill Diego,
you might as well kill me too!
I'd rather die and join him in death!
But you?
As long as you live, no one
will ever love you, Arnaldo!
No one! Because you're a monster!
I'll never forget how
you killed Nanny Carlotta!
And even if you let me live,
I will never love you!
I will never love a criminal!
[Lily] Monster!
-I didn't mean--
-You bastard! I don't love you!
I'll never love a demon like you!
A monster! I don't love you!
-You love me!
-I used you!
I never really loved you.
I'd never fall in love with a criminal!
I'd never fall for an Ardiente!
Stop this!
[Lily] No one will ever love you, Arnaldo!
Because I will never love you!
I will never love you!
[screams]
[gunshot]
[dramatic music playing]
[somber music playing]
Arnaldo. Arnaldo…
[Diego sobbing]
[somber music playing]
Where's my grandson?
[sobs]
No! No! No!
Arnaldo! No!
Arnaldo!
[sobbing]
Arnaldo, why? Why?
Why?!
-Ma'am Emilia.
-Yes?
Your son's gone.
Huh? What do you mean?
Mayor Arnaldo's gone. He's dead.
Dead? Are you nuts?
Stop making up stories. Get out of here!
Arnaldo's dead?
What are you talking about?
He even said he would visit me. He said…
I'll be gone for a while.
You're leaving?
-Yeah. I have to go.
-Huh?
I have to go.
[chuckles]
Arnaldo…
[melancholic music playing]
Arnaldo?
Arnaldo!
Raul!
Mama!
[wailing]
He's gone!
My son!
[melancholic music playing]
Leave me. Leave me!
Leave me! Leave me!
[Julio sobbing]
What did you do to my little boy?
Why did you do this to my grandson?
Arnaldo!
Wh-- Why…
Why did you hurt my little boy?
You didn't listen to me.
I told you… I told you to be careful.
Be careful.
Who… Who did this to you?
My little boy!
Blood will be paid with blood.
I promise you that, Arnaldo.
I… I promise you.
My little boy!
Wh-- Why…
Why did they do this to you?
Why? Why?
[tense music playing]
[melancholic music playing]
Diego.
-Mom.
-Lily, dear.
-Diego.
-Mom.
-We only wanted to…
-Diego, Miss Lily.
Is Arnaldo really gone?
We didn't want Arnaldo to die.
I wish I could've saved him.
Because of what he did…
it's like he had paid for
all the crimes he had done.
He will never hurt anyone again.
Please excuse me.
I'll follow in a bit.
For those of us who've lost loved ones…
with Arnaldo's death…
it just goes to show that
whether you're rich or poor,
powerful or weak,
what you do to others
will always come back to you.
Who did this to you?!
Tell me!
[sobbing]
-Nimfa!
-Mister Fernan!
Nimfa!
Mayor!
[gunshot]
[melancholic music playing]
[bleak music playing]
[sobbing]
Why?
Why did you take my grandson?
Why?!
He wasn't doing anything wrong!
He was a good boy!
Why?
He was…
He was my only hope!
Damn you!
What am I now, huh?
What am I now?
[ominous music playing]
[mumbles]
[gunshot]
Was that a gunshot?
What are you waiting for?
Get the kids inside! Hurry!
-Dude! Dude!
-Where did that come from?
It came from the governor's mansion!
-Thanks, man. Let's go!
-Okay.
[breathing heavily]
[knocking]
Let me out of here!
Let me out of here! Let me out!
[gunshot]
I'm coming for you!
I will be coming for each
and every one of you!
Please let me out!
[whimpering]
[ominous music playing]
[shrieks]
[Julio] No. No…
No!
Dad…
I promised you that
I'd take care of Arnaldo.
I tried to help him change.
But I failed.
I failed, so please forgive me.
I wasn't able to save my brother.
[melancholic music playing]
[somber music playing]
I built an empire
so that you wouldn't have
to lay down on a bed of thorns.
[funeral music playing]
I've killed countless enemies.
All to make sure that
you'd live in paradise.
But in the blink of an eye,
they took you away from me.
[somber music playing]
Rest now, my prince…
for I will burn the whole
town of Ardiente to ashes
to avenge your death.
[somber music playing]
[ominous music playing]
-What do we do?
-We should wait…
-for ma'am and sir.
-Yes, sir.
[ominous music playing]
Sir, somebody left this.
Who's it from?
Julio Ardiente and his threats again.
Mom!
Don't go near the coffins.
Get away from there!
[explosion]
-Head inside!
-Hurry!
[Diego] Go! Stay alert!
[ominous music playing]
Governor.
We already sent the coffins
to Diego and Lily's house.
What's your next move?
We'll ask for the Triad's help.
We will strengthen our forces.
And just like what
my grandson Arnaldo wanted,
we will make Lily and Diego
cry tears of blood.
[ominous music playing]
Dearest children of Poblacion Ardiente…
My grandson, Arnaldo,
was mercilessly killed…
by Lily and Diego Torillo.
They killed your beloved Mayor Arnaldo…
who wanted nothing…
but to improve your lives
and to serve you
to the best of his abilities.
That's why now I'm beseeching you…
We should not allow these monsters
to keep abusing us like this.
Please help me seek justice for
the murder of Mayor Arnaldo.
We need to make sure
these criminals own up to their crimes.
We need to make them pay for their sins.
Help me make Lily and Diego Torillo pay.
Because they are the true criminals.
They are the scum
who want to ruin our town.
That's right.
Justice for the mayor!
-Kill those criminals!
-Kill them!
[chanting] Justice! Justice! Justice!
Justice! Justice! Justice! Justice!
Justice! Justice! Justice!
-Get out of there!
-[clamoring]
-Justice for the mayor!
-Don't cause trouble here!
All you do is cause trouble!
What do you even want to happen?
Just leave! What are you doing?
You're all blind followers.
They paid you to do this!
Ma'am, there's a commotion outside!
[commotion continues]
[Fernan] You can't be here!
Stay alert. And deploy more men.
Yes, ma'am.
[Camia] Diego, Lily…
Julio is manipulating the people
of Ardiente to go against you.
Only his blind followers believe Julio.
But, Lily…
Julio wants revenge.
Please be careful.
He has no right to seek revenge.
Arnaldo ended up that way
because of Julio and Emilia.
Diego, he's already begun.
He can try.
Julio can do whatever he wants,
we're not afraid.
Diego and I didn't do anything wrong.
We didn't kill his grandson.
He killed himself.
No matter what he does,
the public won't believe him.
Because they all know
that Diego and I are
fighting for what's right.
[commotion continues]
Dragon ladies, I need you
to come here now.
Because you have to save my son's life.
He is in danger.
Please, come now. Okay? Now!
And, Raul, where are you? Where are you?!
I need you to save our son's life!
He's in danger! Come on!
Enough, Emilia. Enough.
Stop this insanity.
Your son is dead!
Arnaldo is dead! Do you understand?
Arnaldo is dead.
Lily and Diego killed him.
Do you understand?
He's dead!
[shushes] Papa, no! No! No, no!
You're lying! You're lying! Mama!
Please, let's save him! Please! Come on!
Arnaldo!
Enough. Enough, Emilia.
Stop this nonsense.
We're the only Ardientes left!
Prove to me that you deserve
to be called an Ardiente.
Help me!
Help me seek revenge for your son Arnaldo!
Please!
Please! Please!
[Fernan] All you do is cause trouble!
What do you even want to happen?
Just leave already!
We need to move to a different town.
But our livelihood is here.
What if Governor Julio attacks us?
[woman] We have to move.
It's not safe here anymore.
Uh, excuse me. What's going on here?
The supporters of Governor Julio
are holding a demonstration
in front of Lily Cruz's house.
And yesterday, they planted
bombs in some coffins.
-Lily Cruz lives here?
-Yeah.
But if I were you, I'd stay away
from here to avoid their mess.
-Let's go.
-Thank you.
[commotion continues]
[Helena] Emilia! Help me! I'm on fire!
Snap out of your insanity!
Help me and your son Arnaldo!
Kill them all!
[Helena] Emilia!
[Arnaldo] I… I need you.
I--I need you.
I need you to make them pay for my death.
Mom, I need you.
Make them pay. They killed me.
Wake up! Wake up. Wake up. Wake up.
Mom! Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up!
[ominous music playing]
Hi, Papa. Your favorite daughter is back.
And by the way, I've already
gained the Triad's support.
[Julio] I want the people
of Ardiente to witness
just how I'll mete out my punishment
and wrath on Lily and Diego.
[gunshots]
Where are Anna and Lily?
[guard] They went to see the relatives
of the Ardientes' other victims.
-[gunshots]
-[Lily] Get away from here.
Go to Diego! Tell him
Julio's men ambushed us.
-Lily, I can't leave you--
-I'll be right behind you.
[thud]
[theme music playing]